YURI IKAWA

CONTACT



0411 530 923



mbcrhc@gmail.com



Docklands, VIC

ABOUT

I have developed high level of skills in customer service while working in retail and hospitality industry in the past which allowed me to learn how to deal with customers and give them the best experience possible. Briefly, Have been working as casher at South Melbourne Market and before I have worked as operation officer for half year in Melbourne. In Japan as sales associate at clothing store for 5 years. During this time, I have learned various skills in customer service while maintaining good relationship with customers.

ADDITIONAL INFORMATION

- RSA Certificate holder
- Basic knowledge of KPI & POS register
- CPR First Aid Course
- Basic Life Support Course
- First Aid Training

LANGUAGE

Japanese

English

English

VISA

VISA: Student (Sep 2021)

PERSONAL SKILLS

High hospitality skills and sales skills in customer service industry

Well-Knowledge of Hygiene Practices

Team Spirit, can-do attitude, friendly and professional

Able to keep track of repeated customers. Their likes and dislikes.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

CASHER / SERVER_September 2020 - Present

STEVE'S DELI (SOUTH MELBOURNE MARKET) | Melbourne

- Assisted customers with product selection and queries
- Prepared food: Dipping sauce, cheese, olives etc.
- Removed washed dishes and place them in cabinets accordingly
- Operated cash register

OPERATION OFFICER_October 2019 - April 2020

VFS GLOBAL (VISA APPLICATION CENTER) | Melbourne

- Dealed with customer/applicant queries in person and via e-mail, telephone
- Recorded and maintained all application data into system
- Checked and processed visa application
- Ensured that the entire process is completed within the mandated Time

SALES ASSOCIATE August 2014 - January 2019

PETIT BATEAU JAPAN CO., LTD | Kyoto

3.1 PHILLIP LIM JAPAN LTD., | Kyoto

UNITED ARROWS LTD., | Kyoto

- Set up and displays
- Handled inventory and stocks
- Reviewed merchandize movement
- Prepared daily, weekly, and monthly reports
- Dealed with customer/applicant queries in person and via e-mail, telephone

EDUCATION

KOBE COLLEGE_Bachelor Of Arts, Hyogo, JAPAN | March 2011

GREENWICH ENGLISH COLLEGE_Melbourne, Australia | 3 Months

CODER ACADEMY_Melbourne, Australia | October 2020 - Current